# **LUKASZ TOMASZEWSKI**

**♀** West Sussex, UK

L.R.G.Tomaszewski@gmail.com

in Irgtomaszewski

Mysftz

### Summary

Data scientist with 5+ years experience with Python, with experience in ML, DL and CNN techniques across various libraries and platforms. Specialising in brain computer interface and plant disease classification and further classification using large datasets. Effective leader in management in various fast-paced environments where quality is key. Expertise in improving team performance using efficiency while securing team and customer loyalty and forging a valuable networking base.

## **Work Experience**

### **Kent Sport**

**Duty Assistant** 

♥ University of Kent, UK ☐ Feb 2022-Sept 2022

- Maintained links with students, locals and youth clubs by hosting various and repeating events.
- Upkept events as a university representative such as Lambeth Conference and International fencing competition.
- Ensured clients needs were met and the facilities were clean and safe to use.

#### Kent Union Retail, The Co-op

Duty Supervisor, Accountancy Clerk & Sales Assistant

- Relied on upkeeping the accountancy books for the store as part of Kent Union Retail.
- Oversaw store integrity alone, ensuring the building was opened and closed securely.
- Represented the University as student staff through enagagements with locals and vistors.

### Carphone Warehouse, Dixons Carphone PLC

Operations Manager & Sales Consultant

♥ Crawley, Sussex, UK June 2017 - Mar 2018

- Led multiple regional and divisional teams through our increased sales and target hitting measures.
- Enhanced stock control and accessibility to allow for higher sales and improved customer interaction.
- Controlled banking, stock control for the store and managed shift schedules.

Other work experience in mangerial positions and bar, nightclub and sales environments prior to 2017.

### **Education**

#### Computer Science (Artificial Intelligence), MSc

**♥** University of Kent, UK

₩ Sept 2022

Awarded a postgraduate scholarship and achieved merit grade. Worked 2 jobs, 20+ hours a week to defray maintenence costs. Volunteered for multiple admin roles in the University's Men's Rugby club.

#### Astronomy, Space Science & Astrophysics, BSc (Hons)

• University of Kent, UK

Chosen for a scholarship for academic excellence and achieved a grade of 2:1. Worked 30+ hours a week to defray maintenance costs. Volunteered for admin roles in the University's Men's Rugby club.

Further education also in Mechanical and Aeronautical Engineering. 5 GCSE's held at grade C or above, including Mathematics, English Language and Triple Science.

### **Skills**

### **Computing Languages**

Python, Swift, HTML, CSS, Javascript, Java, R, MySQL, SQLite, LaTeX, R, MatLab, C++

#### **Python Libraries**

Matplotlib, Keras, NumPy, Pandas, Plotly, PyTorch, Scikit-Learn, SciPy, TensorFlow, Seaborn

#### **Personal Skills**

Project Management, Leadership, Decision Making, Ability to Work Under Pressure, Adaptability, Team Communication, Critical Thinking, Time Management, Target Orientated, Conflict Resolution

### **Projects**

### **Brain Computer Interface Classification**

**Masters of Science Thesis** 

Successfully improved the accuracy of a CNN model by 6% within BCI classification on a dataset of EEG reading from patients with Autism Spectrum Disorder using Python, MatLab & Deep Learning techniques.

\_\_\_\_\_

#### Plant 'Cassava' Disease Classification

**♥** University of Kent, UK

**Masters of Science Project** 

Convolutional neural networks ML model for the detection of plant disease classification.

### **Developing Visual & Audio Disabilities Extensions to the HEAT Program**

**Q** University of Kent, UK

Masters of Science Project

∰ Feb 2022

Java based project to develop visual/ audio disability extension features into the HEAT software.

### Magnox Nuclear Waste Disposal

**♀** University of Kent, UK

**Bachelors of Science Thesis** 

₩ Mar 2021

Research of waste control in the UK and the design and development of a new nuclear waste container to optimise storage for the future.

-----

### **Very Near Sun Exploration**

**Q** University of Kent, UK

**Bachelors of Science Thesis** 

∰ Mar 2021

Group research on the design of a spacecraft for very near sun exploration (0-0.2 AU) with Airbus.

Other projects include: Further CNN ML and DL classification evaluration, fairness algorithms analysis, improving

Other projects include: Further CNN, ML and DL classification exploration, fairness algorithms analysis, improving practical data analysis for WEKA software and other Physics based experiments can be found on my GitHub profile.

### **Honours & Awards**

- Nominated for the Team Kent outstanding adminstrator award for the year 2021/22.
- Awarded the Team Kent yellow colours award for 3+ years for volunteer administrative services.
- Awarded the best Men's Rugby commitee member for the year 2021/22.
- Awarded a postgraduate scholarship by the University of Kent.
- Awarded Supervisor of the year by Kent Union Co-op for the year 2020/21.
- Awarded employee of the month by Kent Union Co-op in my first month of employment.
- Awarded a scholarship for academic excellence by the University of Kent upon my initial application.
- Supervised the running University of Kent Men's Rugby team for 3 years, twice winning the annual BUC's men's rubgy southern conference cup.

## **Volunteer Experience**

#### 

## Treasurer & Secretary, Charity & Fundraising Officer

**Q** University of Kent, UK

University of Kent Men's Rugby Club

₩ May 2019 - July 2022

## Anthony Nolan Representative

♥ University of Kent, UK ■ Sept 2021 – June 2022

University of Kent, Kent Marrow Society

### References

References provided within the application process. These referees can be made available upon request.